globbing.com 2018-09-13

# Globbing

## **Overview  **

Our Privacy Policy applies to all visitors, users, and others who access the Service (each, a "User", “you”, “your”). 

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which a collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from Users of the www.globbing.com website ("Site"). 

This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products, Services and any applications made available by Globbing. 

This Privacy Policy affect your legal rights and obligations. If you do not agree to be bound by all of the terms of this Privacy Policy, do not access or use the Service. 

## **1\. Personal information  **

You are free to surf our website without registering. However, in order to use Globbing services, we require you to sign up. All personal information is collected only when you give it to us. Upon sign up you are required to give us your name and email, your home address and contact information. We can also obtain other sort of information in various different manners whilst you use our website. Our servers collect such information as your IP address, language and browser you use, the type of the computer, internet provider, the time and date when you logged in and other such information. That information assists us in understanding and track online behavior and trends of our users.

We also collect information, which follows your movement and tracks the use of our website. That information allows us to give you customized services. The moment you sign up, we store the information provided by you, such as your email, password or else. Globbing may also get additional information about you by means of other customers complaining about you, survey you have completed on our website, you contacting your customer support and others. 

## **2\. Children’s Privacy  **

We do not collect or solicit any information from anyone under the age of 18 or knowingly allow such persons to register for the Service. The Service and its content are not predetermined for children under the age of 18. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 18 without parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. We do not have opportunity to check the validity of information, so we do not bear responsibility for the reasons of use of our website by anyone under the age of 18.

## **3\. Ways we may use your information  **

We can use your information in order to:

• Satisfy your wishes for services, products, and alerts;

• Offer you services and products that might interest you;

• Assist you in using our website;

• Operate your account and alter our services to comply with your preferences;

• Analyze the use of our website in order to improve it, together with products and services we offer;

• Recognize and shield against misuse of our website; and

• Implement our Terms and Conditions.  

## **4\. The protection of Users’ information  **

Globbing takes proper electronic, physical, and other security measures to insure the safety of your personal information from illegal access, modification, or disclosure. All the data provided by you is stored on secure database servers. We password-protect any Globbing profile pages that show your personal information. Globbing will never ask you to disclose your password through phone call or e-mails We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others, except cases predetermined by the law. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and Users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

## **5\. Cookies Policy  **

Globbing has right to use cookies in order to make the work of the Users’ more effective. A miniature text file, which is stored on computer of a user to keep records is called a cookie. There are 2 different ways of cookies – session or persistent cookies. The minute you close your browser a session cookie sees to exist. A persistent cookie stays on your hard drive for prolonged period. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

## **6\. Governing law & Jurisdiction  **

By visiting Site you agree that all issues related to its use and visit this page are regulated by the laws of Republic of Armenia. The emerged disputes are resolved by the commission consisting of two representatives from each Party. In case of failure to come to an agreement the disputes are resolved in accordance with the procedure stipulated by the RA legislation.

## **7\. Changes in Privacy Policy  **

Globbing has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will notify you by the means of email, sent to the most current one, provided to us. Your continued use of Globbing or the Service after any modification to this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such modification.

If your parcel remains in our warehouse for 30 days, you will be charged 1$ for each day thereafter.
